<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">
  <style>
    {% include custom.css %}
  </style>
  
  <p>
    The IPS for Sri Lanka is a document. All the profiles specified by this guide are used by the Sri Lanka IPS Composition and are derived from the <a href="https://hl7.org/fhir/uv/ips/index.html" target="_blank">base IPS specification</a> itself.  
  </p>
  <blockquote class="stu-note">
    <ul>
        <li>Example implementation for each of these profiles can be seen in the <strong>Example tab</strong> of the profile definition.</li>
    </ul>
  </blockquote>

  <h3>HIMS<a name="hims"> </a></h3>
    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hims-ips-bundle.html">IPS Bundle</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the constraints applied to the Bundle resource that is specific to HIMS but derived from the IPS FHIR Implementation Guide.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hims-transactional-bundle.html">Transactional Bundle</a>
      <br />
        This bundle contains all of the HIMS resources for transactional requests.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hims-target-facility-encounter.html">Encounter</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the current facility at which the HIMS patient is receiving health services.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-cvd-risk-category.html">Risk Assessment - Cardiovascular Disease</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's risk for cardiovascular disease.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-follow-up-at-hlc.html">CarePlan - Follow-up At HLC</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the follow-up event for the patient at HLC.
    </p>

  <h3>HHIMS<a name="hhims"> </a></h3>
    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hhims-ips-bundle.html">IPS Bundle</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the constraints applied to the Bundle resource that is specific to HHIMS but derived from the IPS FHIR Implementation Guide.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hhims-transactional-bundle.html">Transactional Bundle</a>
      <br />
        This bundle contains all of the HHIMS resources for transactional requests.
    </p>
  
    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hhims-target-facility-encounter.html">Encounter</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the current facility at which the HHIMS patient is receiving health services.
    </p>

  <h3>Shared<a name="shared"> </a></h3> 
    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-practitioner.html">Practitioner</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the practitioners who participated in the observation and/or procedure.
    </p>

</div>