<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">
  <style>
    {% include custom.css %}
  </style>
  
  <p>
    The IPS for Sri Lanka is a document. All the profiles specified by this guide are used by the Sri Lanka IPS Composition and are derived from the <a href="https://hl7.org/fhir/uv/ips/index.html" target="_blank">base IPS specification</a> itself.
    <br />
    <br />
    For the full list of system generated artifacts for this implementation guide, see <a href="artifacts.html" target="_blank">Artifacts Summary</a>.
  </p>
  <blockquote class="stu-note">
    <ul>
        <li>Example implementation for each of these profiles can be seen in the <strong>Examples tab</strong> of the profile definition.</li>
    </ul>
  </blockquote>

  <h3>HIMS<a name="hims"> </a></h3>
    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hims-ips-bundle.html">IPS Bundle</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the constraints applied to the Bundle resource that is specific to HIMS but derived from the IPS FHIR Implementation Guide.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hims-transactional-bundle.html">Transactional Bundle</a>
      <br />
        This bundle contains all of the HIMS resources for transactional requests.
    </p>

     <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hims-composition.html">Composition</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the International Patient Summary (IPS) data set for HIMS.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-cvd-risk-category.html">Risk Assessment - Cardiovascular Disease</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's risk for cardiovascular disease.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-follow-up-plan.html">Service Request - Referral Request For Follow-up Plan</a>
      <br/>
        This profile represents the referral request for a Follow-up Plan.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-follow-up-at-hlc.html">CarePlan - Follow-up At HLC</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the follow-up event for the patient at HLC.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-medical-history.html">Condition - Medical History</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents previous, pre-existing and new conditions for the patient.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-random-blood-sugar.html">Observation - Random Blood Sugar</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's RBS results.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-fasting-blood-sugar.html">Observation - Fasting Blood Sugar</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's FBS results.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-blood-pressure.html">Observation - Blood Pressure</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's blood pressure.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-total-cholesterol.html">Observation - Total Cholesterol</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's total cholesterol results.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-risk-behaviour-physical-activity.html">Observation - Physical Activity Status</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the physical activity status of the patient.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-risk-behaviour-tobacco-smoker.html">Observation - Tobacco Smoker</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the tobacco smoking status of the patient.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-height.html">Observation - Patient Height</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's height.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-bmi.html">Observation - BMI</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's BMI.
    </p>

     <p><a href="StructureDefinition-no-allergy-intolerance.html">Allergy Intolerance - No Allergy Information Available</a>
        <br />
        This profile indicates that there is no allergy information available for the patient.
    </p>
   

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-no-medication-requested.html">Medication Request - No Prescriptions</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the fact that the patient has not received any prescriptions for drugs.
    </p>

  <h3>HHIMS<a name="hhims"> </a></h3>
    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hhims-ips-bundle.html">IPS Bundle</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the constraints applied to the Bundle resource that is specific to HHIMS but derived from the IPS FHIR Implementation Guide.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hhims-transactional-bundle.html">Transactional Bundle</a>
      <br />
        This bundle contains all of the HHIMS resources for transactional requests.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-hhims-composition.html">Composition</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the International Patient Summary (IPS) data set for HHIMS.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-drug-dispensation.html">Medication Dispense</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents dispensed medication for an HHIMS patient.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-notifiable-diseases-notified.html">Communication - Notifiable Diseases Notified</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents a message communicated to the practitioner about a patient's encounter.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-imaging-study.html">Imaging Study</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the content or results of a imaging study.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-no-medical-history.html">Condition - Medical History Not Available</a>
      <br />
        This profile indicates that there is no information available about the subject's health problems or disabilities.
    </p>

    
   <p><a href="StructureDefinition-allergy-intolerance.html">Allergy Intolerance</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the allergy information available for the patient.
    </p>


    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-medication-request.html">Medication Request</a>
        <br />
        This profile is to record requests for medication that are prescribed to a patient or for Non-Medical Supplies Division (MDS) medicines.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-procedures-request.html">Service Request - Procedures</a>
        <br />
        This profile initiates a request for a procedure.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-investigations-request.html">Service Request - Investigations</a>
        <br />
        This profile initiates a request for an investigation.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-imaging-request.html">Service Request - Imaging</a>
        <br />
        This profile initiates a request for imaging to be done.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-referral-task.html">Task - Referral Task</a>
        <br />
        This profile is used to track the progress of a patient's referral.
    </p>

  <h3>Shared<a name="shared"> </a></h3> 
   <p><a href="StructureDefinition-ips-patient.html">Patient</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents demographics and other administrative information about an HIMS or HHIMS individual receiving care or other health-related services.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-target-facility-encounter.html">Encounter</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the current facility at which the HIMS or HHIMS patient is receiving health services.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-practitioner.html">Practitioner</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the practitioners who participated in the observation and/or procedure.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-weight.html">Observation - Patient Weight</a>
      <br />
        This profile represents the patient's weight.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-providers-location.html">Location</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the physical location of the provider.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-organization.html">Organization</a>
        <br />
        This profile represents the organization providing health related services.
    </p>

    <p><a href="StructureDefinition-device-information.html">Device Information</a>
        <br />
        This profile is used to record key information about the system that contributed to the patient’s record.
    </p>

</div>